[white noise playing]
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Sound machine off.
God damn it.
[sighs]
[gargles]
-You good. dog?
-Yeah. Waiting to hear from Wharton.
Who's Wharton?
Wanna hear something really cute?
-I think I'm in love again.
-Aw. Is that who I heard over last night?
Oh. my God. You heard that?
-Yeah.
-Yeah. you know
the hot French foreign exchange student?
Her name...
-No.
-...kinda rhymes with "cappuccino."
Dude. relax. Why are you tweaking
over a summer camp?
It is. uh... It's not a summer camp.
It's the most elite program
of any business school.
AKA my dream school. AKA fast track
to getting into that school.
AKA the most important moment of my life.
-It's literally summer.
-Yeah. the summer before senior year.
-Exactly. Who cares?
-College admissions officers.
You're 17. You act like you're 30.
Don't you think you're gonna regret
not spending your summer going buck wild?
Not really. No.
-Morning.
-Hi. Morning.
-I got bagels.
-Thanks.
Ooh. Hero.
Okay. How we doing?
Have we heard from Wharton?
Not yet.
-And she's being really chill about it.
-Great.
-[gasps]
-[Steven] What? Is that it?
Yes? No?
Hmm? Huh?
[Connor] Did you get in?
[Steven] Connor? She's crying.
[Connor] I can't tell
if she's happy or devastated.
How are you twins?
-You guys--
-[Steven] Annie. are you okay?
-Mmm-hmm. I'm just processing.
-[Steven] Okay.
[Steven] Yeah?
The end of the life
I once imagined for myself.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. Hey. can I hug?
-Please?
-Hmm. yeah.
-Everything's over. It's okay.
-Okay.
-Thank you. Um...
-I love you.
-I think good on hug now.
-Okay. I'm out.
Look. if they don't want you.
it's their loss.
[Annie] It's literally...
I love you so much for saying that.
thanks. But it's literally my loss.
-Legitimately. in a literal sense.
-What if we look at it as a good thing?
You know? You're 17. You deserve
to have some fun. You could travel.
-You could go to Greece with Connor.
-Hey. whoa! No. no. no.
-That's a trip for me and Capoochie.
-[Steven] Who?
[Connor] Why don't you go to Thailand
with your 100% heterosexual
straight boyfriend?
I cannot break up with him
till he's ready to come out.
We've been together since sixth grade.
Could be bi.
-Fair.
-And her name is Capucine.
If you'll give her HPV.
at least say it right.
-I don't have HVP.
-I know you don't. You have HPV.
Annie. I promise it'll be okay.
Try not to get too worked up.
Especially over a summer camp.
It's a summer program.
-[coughs] Camp.
-Dude.
[hesitates] Can we all...
-Summer program.
-[Steven] Yeah.
-Annie didn't get into the summer program.
-Camp.
I messed it up again.
I'm so sorry. Uh-uh.
It's a summer program.
[Connor] Damn. you're right.
-It's a summer camp.
-I agree.
-[Connor] Did it again. Sorry.
-Summer program.
Wait. Did I get my HPV vaccine?
'Cause she's right.
This shit is everywhere.
-You're good.
-Wait. No. Dad. for real.
This shit gives you butthole cancer.
Yeah. it does.
Uh. symptoms for HPV.
Let's watch Cynthia Erivo sing "Edelweiss"
at the Kennedy Center over and over.
It is incredibly healing.
I already did that.
-What?
-Yeah. It didn't even help.
-What am I gonna do this summer now?
-I don't know. You could...
-start SSRIs?
-Yeah.
But I feel I have
an addictive personality. so...
You know what I could do?
I could come to Thailand with you now.
[chuckles awkwardly]
Oh.
That could be cool.
Is there a reason you wouldn't want me
to come?
No. No. Not at all. I would love that.
I guess I just...
[clears throat]
I guess I was kind of expecting
this summer to be like
a "do our own thing" kinda vibe.
I'm sorry. Are you. like...
-saying we should break up for the summer?
-No.
-[chuckling] Annie. no.
-Okay.
What? No. I just...
-Unless you wanna break up for the summer.
-Okay. Oliver. let's just...
-Sure.
-It's all good. Are... What's happening?
I would say you... uh...
-'Sup. pimps?
-Connor!
-Grandpa died.
-What?
But not "grandpa" grandpa. Mom's dad.
The one who apparently sucks.
I'm sorry. Sucked.
What's up. Oliver? I love the haircut.
Thanks. You guys have a second grandpa?
Our mom's dad. But you know
how we can't talk about her
because our dad gets dark and sad?
The same thing goes with this grandpa.
We haven't seen him since Mom died.
-So your entire lives?
-Yeah. Apparently. he was shady as fuck
-and everyone hated him.
-How'd you know he died?
Someone from a lawyer's office called
and started talking legal.
And I was like. "Shit. Help.
I need a grown-up.
-My sister will call you--"
-I will.
You just need to leave 'cause we were
having a conversation.
-You and me? No.
-Yeah.
-Okay.
-No. we weren't.
-No. we were. This is rude.
-And it's not...
It's not as important
as the death of an estranged grandpa.
Almost nothing is.
-You guys should talk.
-Thank you.
-I'm so sorry for your loss.
-Thanks.
Okay. [grunts]
[chuckles]
-Love you. babe.
-Bye.
[door opens]
[door closes]
-Was he finally about to come out?
-I'm gonna kill you.
-No! [screams]
-I'm gonna end your fucking life!
[Marjorie] Well.
thank you for meeting me.
No personal notes
beyond these instructions.
so I'll just get straight to it.
All right. Gordon has left you. Steven.
nothing.
And to Connor and Annie Jacobson.
Gordon has made you the beneficiaries
of his trust.
which you'll gain control over
when you turn 18.
Uh. it includes...
property on a parcel of land in Canada.
-He's Canadian?
-[Connor] Don't fuck with Canada.
[Marjorie] Yes. In Muskoka.
-I have for-real. like. wolf phobia.
-[Annie] Does that mean Mom was Canadian?
-Accent's too thick. Don't understand it.
-Nobody here is Canadian. [clears throat]
-Can we please...
-Yeah. Uh...
-Sorry.
-Gordon also left
these letters for Annie and Connor.
-Thank you very much.
-Sorry.
Can we read the letters?
We'll discuss this later.
I gotta get to work.
-[Annie] Dad. those are for us.
-[Steven] Yeah. [clears throat]
-Hey.
-Yes?
Anything else about this matter
comes directly to me.
You understand?
Okay.
And. again. I am so sorry
about your grandfather's passing.
-It's fine. We didn't know him.
-[Annie] Connor.
[slow piano music playing]
Really? Your birthday?
[suspenseful music playing]
[slow music playing]
[sputters]
Okay. [clears throat]
"Annie. My biggest regret
is not fighting harder to see you."
"It wasn't because I didn't love you."
"I shouldn't have agreed to the plan.
I'm sorry."
"I hope Sterling Point
will reveal the truth."
"It was your mother's favorite place
on earth." [inhales sharply]
"But most importantly. Annie. find her."
"She will need you after I'm gone.
Love. Gordon."
[breathing heavily]
[whispering] Fuck.
[sighs]
Thank you. baby. Should I say "bonjour"?
It's "merci."
[Annie] Hey. Connor.
I really need to talk to you for a second.
Oh. hi. Are you Capucine? Hi.
I'm Annie. So nice to meet you.
Her English isn't very good.
-I'm fluent in English.
-What? No.
-Yeah. God.
-Connor. I need you to focus
'cause this is sort of a pressing issue.
Gordon has been writing us letters
our entire lives. Dad hid 'em in a safe.
Wait. We have a safe?
Did you find diamonds in there?
Beautiful gems?
Connor! The last letter that Gordon wrote.
he said. "Find her."
-Find who?
-Exactly! Something's going on.
We have to figure out
what's happening right now.
He's not even biologically related to us.
Now he's dead. What does it matter?
It doesn't matter to you that
Dad's been lying to us our entire lives?
Oh. you guys are adopted.
Yeah. Our parents tried to have kids.
but our dad shoots blanks. so...
[Annie] He is my only biological relative.
-I need to go to Canada.
-[Connor] If you're gonna dig into shit.
go for it.
but please don't ruin this for me.
I'm not trying to ruin anything for you.
But can you. like. cover for me
if I were to go?
-Say I'm in Thailand with Oliver.
-Yeah. sure. Whatever.
We have to go pack
for our flight to Ibiza.
-I thought you were going to Greece.
-Yes. Ibiza. Greece. Dumbass.
Right.
[slow piano music playing]
[sighs]
[whispering] Sorry. Dad.
Sorry.
["Lover Girl" by Laufey playing]
Excuse me. Could I have a pillow
and a blanket. please?
We only provide those on flights
longer than two hours.
-but lemme see what I can find--
-The flight isn't longer than two hours?
We're in New York City. ma'am.
Headed to Toronto.
It's a 45-minute flight.
-Forty-five minutes?
-[Avery] Uh-huh.
To Canada?
[Avery] Mmm-hmm.
But I just took an Ambien.
[seatbelt light beeps]
[mouthing]
[male pilot] Flight attendants.
please prepare the cabin for landing.
[yawns]
[propeller droning]
[softly] Where the fuck am I?
[male voice] Annie?
-Yeah. Hi.
-Hi. yeah. Ellis. your pilot.
-Nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you too.
I'll be flying you to Muskoka.
[chuckles]
Um. can I take your stuff?
-Thank you so much.
-Yeah. no worries. [grunts]
Sorry. Hey.
Oh. sorry.
-We're goin' this way.
-Yeah.
No. [chuckles] You're good.
Please tell me
this isn't how we're getting there.
[Ellis] No. No. hell no.
That's how we're getting there.
The plane in the water?
-Yes. The plane--
-No! Dude. no. I can't...
What? What's wrong?
I didn't know that it would be
a plane in water.
I can't do that.
You could drive there. You just gotta be
careful not to hit a moose.
-'Cause it might get hurt.
-What's happening?
And also you die. instantly.
I'm sorry. Are you old enough
to fly an airplane?
[scoffing] God. no.
No. I just control it with the remote.
[Annie sarcastically] That's just amazing.
'cause now I feel really safe getting
into this boat plane thingy with you.
[Ellis] It's called a seaplane.
-but "boat plane" sounds way better.
-I knew that.
My brain is slightly fucked up.
I'm a little high on Ambien right now.
-You're high. like--
-No. I'm not "high" high.
-I don't do drugs.
-Right. no. No. I don't do drugs either.
Except when I'm flying this thing.
-[chuckles]
-Then I go crazy.
I take all the drugs I can find.
-Are you joking?
-Yeah.
I've never even smoked weed.
-No. I thought... Oh.
-Yeah.
Had to double-check.
So. coming?
-Now?
-Yeah.
Yeah.
-It's rocking everywhere. Is that normal?
-Yeah. I know.
No. it is. You're good.
-You ready?
-Yeah.
Yeah.
["Don't Speak" by Loaded Honey playing]
-[Annie] Did we land?
-Yeah. You're good.
-You can open your eyes now.
-We're on the water still.
-[Ellis chuckles]
-This is actually really beautiful though.
-[Ellis] It's nice. eh?
-Yeah.
[Ellis] All right.
Well. welcome to Sterling Point.
It's a great little island.
-This is an island?
-Yeah. Yes.
Yeah. it's an island.
How'd you find this place?
Uh. through some mutual friends.
[Ellis] Oh. okay. 'Cause it's
the first time it's been rented.
Well. actually. the old owner told me
he'd never rent it out.
-Just hold on.
-[Annie] Yeah.
[grunts]
-[grunting]
-You knew him?
-Uh. yeah.
-Thanks.
Everyone knew Gordon.
Well. I have another pickup.
Canada Day rush.
Wait. Oh. are... Uh. where do I get stuff?
Like more drugs?
-Like food. maybe.
-Right.
Yeah. You gotta rent a boat
to get off the island to get that stuff.
-And how do I do that?
-Just walk through the East Woods.
Find the sign "Sterling Point Marina."
-Did Gordon own the marina?
-Yeah. Yeah. he...
He owned this entire island. actually.
[engine starts]
Oh. my God!
Great.
This isn't what...
[grunts]
[door creaks]
Hello?
[sentimental music playing]
[softly] Hey. Mom.
You were hot. Mom.
[glass breaking]
Hello?
[thudding]
Fuck.
[objects clattering]
Hello?
[yells]
Why are there nuts everywhere?
[window creaking]
["Jingle Bells" chiming]
Yeah. I'm not sleeping here.
-[birds chirping]
-Mom. I am so sorry.
I do not think island is my vibe.
[insects buzzing]
[people chattering indistinctly]
[sighs]
Thank God.
[people chattering and laughing]
-Hi.
[woman] Can I help you?
Uh. yeah. actually.
I'm staying on the island.
and someone told me I had to rent a boat
to get stuff on the mainland.
Oh. yeah. yeah. we can help with that.
Although. um.
I don't know what we have left.
You know what? I have to head to work.
But my husband can definitely
help you find something.
-Amazing. Thanks.
-Okay. You're welcome.
It's just up here.
-Joe?
-[Joe] Yeah.
Hey. can you help...
I'm so sorry. I didn't get your name.
No worries. Annie.
Can you help Annie with a rental?
I have to work.
-I'll see what I got.
-Great.
-Nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you. Thanks so much again.
Sorry. It is Canada Day. So it is busy.
Totally. I actually just found out
that I'm half Canadian.
So. good timing. I guess. right?
-Half is better than none.
-[chuckles]
Did you know the guy
that owned the marina?
[Joe] I did.
Was he nice?
He was. Very.
Did he have family that came here?
Anything like that?
Why do you ask?
No reason. really.
Okay. I found a tinner.
so all I'm gonna need is a copy
of your driver's license
and your boater license. please.
Um...
You know what the craziest thing is?
I don't have either of those.
Okay. I can't legally rent you one
without at least one of those things.
Have you actually ever.
I don't know. driven a boat?
Um...
-Not that I recall.
-Right. tell you what.
I'm gonna have my son give you
a quick lesson.
and then we'll see
if you can take one out on your own.
Thank you so much. That sounds great.
-All right.
-Really appreciate that.
I bet.
He should've been back by now.
[Oona] I'll give her some lessons. Joe.
[Joe] How do you even hear wh--
I hear everything you say in the office.
You know how sound travels over water.
You taught me that.
Don't let her. Joe. She can't even park
our boat. She makes me do it.
Okay. Maple! I let you do that one time
to make you feel special. okay? So shush.
-Hey. beautiful.
-Hi. Hey.
-I'm Oona.
-I'm Annie. Nice to meet you.
-Beautiful name for a beautiful girl.
-Thanks.
I'll take the keys. Joe.
Okay. calm it down. One. And you may be
the worst boat driver I've ever seen.
-The fuck? That's not true.
-Tell me.
When approaching a red buoy.
what do you do?
-Ask her out to dinner.
-So close. Incorrect.
-[Oona] It's a joke.
-Told you.
Come on. Come on. Joe. You know me.
-We go way back. Please.
-"Way back"?
Joe. baby. my guy. I can handle her.
You've seen what I can handle.
I can handle her.
Or let me cover the marina desk.
Babe. which one
am I least likely to fuck up?
-Thanks. I'll take the keys. Come with me.
-Awesome. Thanks so much.
-Get ready for the ride of your life.
-Yeah.
Your sister is outta control.
Yep.
Have you ever given a hand job before?
Uh...
-Well--
-So. so you just twist
and then steer in the direction
you wanna go. all right?
More twisty. more speedy. Got it?
-No.
-It's easy. You can't mess it up.
-[Annie] No. I--
-Yeah. come on.
It's okay.
-Sorry. I'm sorry.
-Yeah.
Okay.
-Okay. Yeah.
-Nice. All right.
-Uh. so I just kinda hit it?
-Yeah. just twist it.
-Remember. just twisty. speedy.
-Twisty. speedy.
Okay? Ready?
It's just twisty. speedy.
Yeah.
Whoa!
-Okay. Yeah.
-Whoa! Whoa!
-Okay.
-Whoa.
-Whoa! No. no. Oona.
-Okay.
Wait. Annie. just let go.
-[screaming]
-Annie. stop the boat!
-Let go of it!
-I don't know how!
-Fuck! Let go! Let go!
-[screaming] Oh. my God!
-Let go! We're leaning into it.
-[screaming] I don't know how to stop!
-Crazy. baby! You're crazy!
-Oona!
-Whoo-hoo!
-Fuck!
Okay. I'm feeling a bit sick though now.
So could you stop?
-You never taught me that!
-Actually stop. Annie. I'm gonna be sick!
-What do I do?
-Let go!
-[Annie screaming]
-Fucking hell!
-Okay. Okay.
-Yeah. okay. Okay. Good.
Whoa. Okay.
That was good. that's good. Well done.
Right. Um...
So. what you're saying is
you've never given a hand job before.
[laughing] Actually. I have.
Fuckin' hell. Poor guy. Jesus.
-Hey.
-Dude. happy Canada Day.
Yeah.
What are you doing tonight
for the fireworks?
Um. probably Island K or something.
Nice. I'll tell you what.
I'll be down on the dock with a bunch
of brewskis if you wanna join me after.
Cool.
Hey. um. is it weird
that girl's renting Gord's cottage?
We'd have heard if the island
had been sold or something. right?
What girl is renting his cottage?
The girl with the dark. curly hair. Annie?
No. I'm sure he...
I'm sure he hasn't sold the place.
Fuckin' hope not.
You want me to help you with something?
-No.
-No?
No. I got a few more things
I gotta do anyway.
-Okay. See ya.
-Have fun.
It's probably annoying people asking this.
but where are you from?
-Where am I from?
-Feel like it's not Canada?
-No. I was trying to hide my accent.
-Were you?
Damn. yeah.
'Cause people say it's intimidating.
Yeah. it's extremely hot.
You think it's hot.
Yeah. Does anyone not think
a British accent is hot?
Um. where am I from?
I'm basically from wherever
my mum's boyfriends happen to be from.
So I was born in Amsterdam.
and then I spent a few heavenly years
in Paris.
-Very cool.
-And then way too fucking long in London.
and then here. for a guy named Hank.
-Fuck.
-Yeah.
But then recently. my mum decided
something isn't vibing for her internally.
And she fucked off to India for the summer
to open her chakras.
and I was like. "Yeah. no. I'm okay."
-Yeah. what does that mean?
-I couldn't fuckin' tell you.
I'm only talking about me.
-Tell me about you.
-I wanna hear everything.
I wanna know more about you.
Why's a Toronto girlie here by herself?
Toronto girlie?
I'm a New York girlie. actually.
-Ooh. okay. Cool. A Yank.
-Yeah.
-Yeah. a Yank.
-Fun. Wait. why Muskoka?
Um. my mom would spend summers
around here sometimes. so I'm...
And she died. so I wanted
to see the place she loved.
-Okay. Shit. I'm sorry.
-No.
Thank you. I never really know what to say
when people say that. 'cause I'm like...
It was so long ago that it's not sad.
Right. So it's just. like.
deep. not-dealt-with.
core-mother-wound sad.
Hmm. Interesting.
Hi.
Uh. I'm gonna need to see
some ID. ma'am.
Yeah. sure.
Um. shit.
I actually think I forgot my ID
at your mum's place last night.
Oh. man. you were fucking my mom again?
Both of them. actually. At the same time.
-I'm exhausted.
-Put your fingers away.
Put them down. you monster.
-Too far. Crossed a line. My bad.
-Too far. We draw the line there.
Those are my parents.
-Sorry...
-It's cool. You know each other. right?
-Yeah. Sully. meet Annie.
-Okay.
-Needed to make sure.
-Annie? Sully. Nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you.
-Hello. Welcome.
-Thank you so much.
-That was a royal bow. if you didn't know.
You know. in honor of the king
for Canada Day.
Is Canada Day for him?
-Is there a king?
-I don't know.
That'll be $10.000. please.
-Sweet. yeah. But free for me?
-Free? Yes. free for Oona.
-You don't have to do that.
-No. it's all good.
Just know you're ripping off
a woman-owned small business. so...
Wanna sit with that for a second?
-Awesome.
-[Annie] I'll cover it.
-Thanks. You sure?
-Of course. I got you.
-Cool.
-Here we go.
-Yeah.
-A nice little tote for little Miss Annie.
-Little Miss Annie.
-That's all you. girl.
-Thank you.
-Of course.
Sully. I don't know how busy you are.
but I was gonna make her some food.
-Would you like to join?
-You're making her food? I'm helping?
-Yeah. Please? Yes. Shall we?
-I'm helping. Right now?
-I'm stripping now! Don't tell my parents.
-[Oona] Cool. Come on.
-I'm coming. I'm coming.
-[Oona] Take it off!
-Okay. Let's go.
-Okay.
[sighs softly]
[phone ringing]
-Hello?
-Hey. this is Joe Anderson calling.
I'm sorry I missed your call.
Perfect timing.
You're on my call sheet for tomorrow.
Listen. I don't mean to interrupt you.
Do Goldie's kids know about the island?
Yes. I delivered them the estate paperwork
and some things
Gordon left them this week.
Have you talked to her yet?
No. I haven't. Um...
I will track her down this week. though.
-Please let me know when you guys connect.
-Yes. ma'am.
Also. Annie and Connor
didn't seem familiar with Gordon
or the assets he left them. so...
I wouldn't be surprised
if they wanted to pay a visit soon.
At least Annie.
So I suggest you find her
before Annie does.
Thank you. ma'am. I appreciate it.
-[Annie] You know what? I love Canada.
-[Oona] Yeah.
-[Annie] This is so wholesome.
-It's so nice.
-This is very cute.
-You think this is nice?
This is the poor area. You should see
the rich people houses. It's insane.
It's a weird mix of people here.
So you got the locals who leave all summer
to rent out their houses.
And they charge a lot of money.
which is very fair enough.
Then you've got the super-rich tourists
who come in. they buy the cottages.
tear them down. build mega-mansions.
-It's a lot.
-Yeah.
It's not great. but the parties are cray.
So it's kinda worth it.
Yeah. And also. the celebrities
-are next-level.
-Yeah?
Really fuckin' famous people.
and really beautiful famous people.
-[laughs] Okay.
-Last summer.
I saw Kaia Gerber on her dock.
She was looking insane.
And I swear to God. we made eye contact.
-and we held the eye contact.
-Okay.
And then she winked at me.
She winked at me.
-It was an invitation. Kinda like--
-[clicks tongue] Like a...
Kill me. Kill me. So the next day.
I was trying to kayak past again.
-Wore my best bikini.
-I'm on the edge of my seat.
-And she wasn't there.
-No!
-And I haven't seen her since. so...
-Okay. that's our mission. I guess.
It's my mission daily.
-Pretty much.
-Obviously. It's probably her mission too.
She's probably thinking about you.
"Who's that blonde girl
with the curly hair and where did she go?"
-I wish. Yeah.
-"I made a mistake!"
-This is exciting.
-Yeah.
Wait. Do you live here. on the boat?
-Where do you live?
-Yeah. this is my crib.
-It's yours. So cool.
-It's my house.
Technically. it's my mum's place.
Where are you staying?
In the. uh... In the green cottage?
The green... What? Gordon's place?
Yeah.
-I guess so. You know Gordon?
-Oh. Yes.
I feel like everybody really knew him.
-Yeah. he was the fucking best.
-Really?
-Yeah. that's crazy.
-I heard he was kinda mean.
-Who said that?
-[Ellis] Hey. Um...
You guys ready?
-Hey.
["Nice To Each Other"
by Olivia Dean playing]
Great.
So. you've... You've met.
Uh. yeah. For. like. a sec.
-[laughing]
-Watch your head!
-Hey.
Okay. what is the deal
with the no-service thing?
I mean. that's kind of the deal.
No.
-Yeah.
-No. I'm sorry. That cannot be real.
-Okay.
-It is.
Okay. Okay.
So you're telling me that at night.
when you get in bed.
you don't look at your phone? You just--
Nope. Just close my eyes and fall asleep.
Wow.
Okay.
Yeah. I mean. it takes everyone a second.
but I don't know.
Once you get used to it.
it's kinda the best.
Actually. my brother did not think
that it was summer in Canada.
-Which is cool.
-Oh. my God.
Yeah.
Yeah. I picked up a guy once
that had all his ice-fishing gear
'cause he thought the lakes stay frozen.
That's so much worse. It makes me feel
like my brother is not that stupid.
-Well... [chuckles]
-Yeah. fair.
Do you live here year-round?
Yeah.
-That's really cool.
-Mmm-hmm.
So. do you know what's gonna happen
to the island now?
[Ellis] I don't know.
I hope it can stay this way.
What do you mean?
Just. Gordon. he could've made millions.
Now. no one's sure what's gonna happen.
Could get sold to some developer.
and we'd all be fucked.
Yeah.
It can't be worth. like. that much. right?
I mean. an island that was half this size
sold last year for like. $9 million. so...
-Sorry. what did you say?
-Yeah. I know.
That's why it's kinda crazy
he never sold out.
I honestly sometimes wonder why.
Hey. guys. Do you wanna go to a party
in Rosseau tonight?
Um. will there be rich dickheads
in attendance?
Almost entirely exclusively.
Wait. The party's in Rosseau? Kaia.
-Yeah!
-[Oona] That's where Kaia lives.
-Kaia?
-This is my chance.
-We need to take Maple home.
-[Maple] Why?
Because you're 12.
and I do have some boundaries.
Can I at least have one beer
on the way back?
-[Sully] No!
-Yeah.
-No. No.
-Bad girl.
-Why would you even ask that? What?
Crazy. [mouthing]
["Views" by Drake playing]
[Annie] Holy shit.
Yeah. His parents are
big real-estate people.
[whooping]
Let's see what you got.
How we doing? How we doing?
-Oh. my God!
-Beautiful women.
Look at the beautiful women.
Guys. I'm gonna run to the bathroom
really quick.
-Yeah. There should be one over there.
-Okay.
-Thank you. See you inside.
-We'll be over here.
Hey. sorry. I'm just gonna...
Wait. Annie? Annie Jacobson?
-Hi.
-What?
-Hey.
-What the hell? Wait. what?
Rory. Yeah.
What's Annie J from middle school
doing in Canada? Is Connor here?
No. I'm with some of my friends.
-I'm so happy to see you. This is insane.
-Yeah.
Can I give you a tour?
-Wait. this is your house?
-Yeah.
Yeah. This is my boathouse.
to the cottage. as the Canadians say.
Dude. let me show you around.
-Yeah. Yeah.
-Please?
-Come on.
-Yeah.
Jesus Christ.
This is so beautiful.
This view looks like a fake backdrop.
Oh. it is. It's CGI.
-Nice. That's really smart.
-Yeah.
No. I'm kidding.
-Just through here.
-Thank you.
It's so nice to see you.
Thanks. Yeah. really good to see you.
I feel like I haven't seen you
since middle school graduation.
I was gonna say. I saw you last year
at Noah Greenberg's after-prom?
Oh. my God. yeah. Do you know him?
I don't even. but my date did.
-which didn't work out.
-Oh. sorry.
But. yeah. I remember.
You looked really beautiful.
-[chuckles awkwardly]
-What? You did.
Holy shit!
-No! Jacobson?
-Hello.
-What's goin' on over here. man?
-Good to see you. Lincoln.
-You too. What are you doing here?
-Not much.
Yeah. I'mma...
Nah. I don't dap up my boys' girls.
Right. right. right? This guy got hot. no?
-God. okay. Don't answer that.
-Nah. you know what I'm talkin' about.
Yo. she's... Look at her. though.
But I always knew you had potential.
I knew it.
-Good shit. bro.
-[Rory] Later. man.
-You remember Lincoln. right?
-Yeah. What a charmer.
-Yeah.
-Charming as ever.
-He's got a place up here as well.
-Oh. really?
Yeah. Wait. so why are you here?
Why are you in Muskoka?
Besides. you know. what is obviously fate.
Yes. I knew this was your house.
I'm here to kill you.
-Okay. Right.
-Sorry. I don't know why I said that.
-"I'm here to kill you."
-No. you're just fully stalking me.
-Yes.
-Makes sense.
-Not the first time. honestly. Yes.
-Really? You have a stalker?
-I got a couple. Yeah.
-Thought I was the only one.
-No. I got a couple already.
-That's cool.
No. seriously. why are you in Muskoka?
[chuckles] I...
I honestly don't really have a plan.
I'm kinda just here.
-What?
-You don't have a plan?
You're Annie Jacobson. What do you mean?
You had an internship in sixth grade.
-[chuckles]
-You don't have a plan?
-How do you remember that?
-It was crazy.
-It wasn't totally an internship.
-Okay. I'm sorry.
But. yeah. I guess my mom used
to spend time here.
so I'm just checking it out.
-Okay. nice.
-Yeah.
Same. My mom has been
coming up here for forever.
Before I was born.
Oh. wow.
Yeah. She owns. like. half this lake now.
That's crazy. 'cause our moms
knew each other. right?
Yeah. Did they?
-Oh. I thought so.
-Yeah. I guess they did. You know what? I...
Actually. is your mom here?
I haven't seen Denise in so long.
I would love to say hey to her.
-Yeah. she's downstairs. God. let's go.
-Cool.
She'd love to see you.
[line ringing]
Pick up.
Hey. this is Annie Jacobson.
leave a message.
Come on.
Why have your fuckin' phones in your hands
all day if you don't even answer 'em?
[line ringing]
[dance music playing]
-Hey. it's Oliver. Leave a message.
-Great. Great.
Mother!
There she is. Mom!
-What?
-Look.
-Hi.
-Oh. my. Annie Jacobson!
Hi. Denise.
The last time I saw you.
you hadn't even started your period yet.
-[chuckles awkwardly]
-And I only know that
because I asked your housekeeper.
I was worried about you at that age.
You know. without a mom.
[Rory] Mom...
Was somebody there for you
when you got your period?
Um...
Yeah.
-Yeah.
-Nice.
-Good.
-Yeah.
Oh. and look at you now.
My God. you're beautiful.
-Thanks.
-How are you. honey? How's your dad?
-You know what? Everybody's good.
-Is he dating anyone?
-He... No.
-Oh. my God. What a waste.
-He's so hot. He's like a smokestack.
-Mom.
Do you know we only discovered Muskoka
because of your parents?
We came up here with them one summer
before you guys were born.
-[Rory] This is true.
-Really?
Annie. your mother...
Oh. my God. she was so upset that
she couldn't be with you and your brother.
And honestly. I understand.
I think that's what
finally led her to filing.
Filing? Filing... Filing for what?
For divorce from your... from your father.
You knew that. right?
[voices fading]
Yeah.
-Of course.
-Hey. Annie. baby. Hey.
-Hi.
-How you doing?
Hello.
-[people whooping]
-Whoo!
Um. Kaia Gerber isn't here.
-Sorry. I haven't introduced--
-She got food poisoning
-at the Beckhams' yesterday.
-Okay.
I'm a drink away
from making out with a man.
and we all know that I do not do that.
-So. yeah. it's time to head.
-Yes. Let's do that.
-It was really nice to see you.
-Fire.
-It was really good to see you.
-So good to see you.
-Bye. guys. Thank you for having us.
-Really good to see you.
-I'm Oona. by the way.
-Thanks.
-Oh. wow.
-Wow.
Have a great night. Thank you.
-[Oona] Yeah. okay.
-Be careful. Let's get you on the boat.
[Annie] Okay.
Is she the one
that makes out with all my friends?
Yeah. Yeah. that's her.
-Have I made out with her?
-Not yet.
Let's get you inside.
Um. thank you for walking me home.
Yeah. Of course.
Wait. so if I need something.
and I don't have service.
-what do I...
-Just yell into the abyss.
Oh!
Sick. Okay.
You're safe. though. I promise.
Yeah. this is Canada. right?
Nothing bad happens in Canada.
Actually. no.
Bad shit happens. like. all the time.
Just not on this island. though.
-[chuckles]
-Okay.
-Bye.
-[girl] Hello?
-[gasps] Jesus!
Who are you?
And what are you doing
in my grandfather's cottage?
Connor. I have some very intense news.
Our mom. I think that she had
a secret biological daughter.
-Fuck!
-You said you'd be gone by the morning.
[Ramona] You said you were adopted?
-Yeah.
-So we're not related.
-She hates me.
-Hey!
She doesn't. Ramona is... She's complicated.
Being here. it's like.
"I don't have a mom."
I feel like I want
to punch a wall or something!
Yeah. that's something we call rage.
It's better to make friends with it.
It's only gonna get worse as you age. so...
I just feel like
everything I knew about myself was wrong.
[Rory] That's a scary feeling.
It's good to be messy sometimes.
It's important.
What do you know about my summer?
My summer.
Well done. You just pushed me away
as far as you could.
Your mom was the most fearless person
I've ever known.
[Annie] Growing up and changing
and feeling out of control.
it's really freaky.
But it's also pretty exciting.
Do you feel like you got
the answers you wanted?
I feel like I've barely
scratched the surface.
You said. "No more secrets."
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm